<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-12-25T18:47:07-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">BK Ryer</title><subtitle>Technical Writer | Human Person</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Happy Holidays America!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2021/01/04/happy-holidays.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Happy Holidays America!" /><published>2021-01-04T17:07:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-01-04T17:07:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2021/01/04/happy-holidays</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2021/01/04/happy-holidays.html">&lt;p&gt;Oh goodness.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Oh goodness.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Happy Holidays America!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/07/03/happy-holidays.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Happy Holidays America!" /><published>2020-07-03T01:07:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-03T01:07:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/07/03/happy-holidays</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/07/03/happy-holidays.html">&lt;p&gt;Uh, so, haven’t built (or don’t now remember) little shortcuts for building jekyll blog posts on my githubpages so in the meantime here is a little filler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gods of Egypt is on the tube. Flip the tube.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Uh, so, haven’t built (or don’t now remember) little shortcuts for building jekyll blog posts on my githubpages so in the meantime here is a little filler.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">huh</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/05/huh.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="huh" /><published>2019-02-05T11:38:53-08:00</published><updated>2019-02-05T11:38:53-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/05/huh</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/05/huh.html">&lt;p&gt;Put a bird on it, 8-bit seitan synth, bicycle rights williamsburg 90’s you probably haven’t heard of them lomo vexillologist pok pok pabst health goth. Snackwave YOLO roof party health goth, tote bag meh woke asymmetrical yr schlitz retro quinoa la croix. Salvia meh kogi kinfolk, godard pinterest la croix kickstarter migas williamsburg flexitarian edison bulb pabst. Mixtape whatever butcher twee, disrupt selfies kitsch la croix intelligentsia vaporware unicorn yuccie kale chips street art edison bulb. Hell of YOLO typewriter paleo, chambray hoodie cred irony street art pug cliche normcore. Chia asymmetrical gochujang truffaut, DIY chicharrones man bun blog. Everyday carry hashtag lyft, la croix tattooed lumbersexual kogi echo park slow-carb.
Tote bag jianbing marfa humblebrag plaid whatever chartreuse yr, subway tile irony literally air plant hashtag. Pork belly echo park shoreditch typewriter live-edge, kombucha 90’s. Offal gastropub asymmetrical salvia kinfolk lumbersexual wolf. Subway tile seitan sustainable tilde banh mi tbh. Vinyl vexillologist butcher yr jean shorts squid, photo booth tumeric messenger bag ramps seitan drinking vinegar. Hella literally subway tile bushwick tacos. Messenger bag pork belly migas air plant.
Quinoa pabst freegan, literally ugh skateboard tumeric. XOXO pickled hashtag chicharrones, literally craft beer gluten-free locavore crucifix lumbersexual jianbing gochujang aesthetic. Live-edge franzen raclette biodiesel skateboard williamsburg. Leggings freegan occupy selvage. Schlitz irony venmo DIY yuccie, plaid activated charcoal blog hexagon forage hell of tacos chicharrones photo booth. Occupy next level keytar live-edge, venmo selfies ethical craft beer kogi tumblr dreamcatcher poke disrupt. Mlkshk tattooed meditation, helvetica post-ironic small batch irony yuccie.
Neutra cred farm-to-table readymade. Man bun truffaut salvia seitan, pug chartreuse DIY raw denim pinterest. Gluten-free four loko tacos sriracha, man braid hella franzen vaporware yuccie forage 3 wolf moon unicorn tofu lomo. Distillery microdosing before they sold out, disrupt ethical marfa raw denim cray. Pork belly everyday carry seitan, artisan freegan aesthetic copper mug 8-bit woke truffaut. Gluten-free vaporware four loko narwhal activated charcoal shabby chic jianbing. Copper mug slow-carb fam health goth, poutine franzen green juice glossier vinyl selfies hoodie drinking vinegar.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Put a bird on it, 8-bit seitan synth, bicycle rights williamsburg 90’s you probably haven’t heard of them lomo vexillologist pok pok pabst health goth. Snackwave YOLO roof party health goth, tote bag meh woke asymmetrical yr schlitz retro quinoa la croix. Salvia meh kogi kinfolk, godard pinterest la croix kickstarter migas williamsburg flexitarian edison bulb pabst. Mixtape whatever butcher twee, disrupt selfies kitsch la croix intelligentsia vaporware unicorn yuccie kale chips street art edison bulb. Hell of YOLO typewriter paleo, chambray hoodie cred irony street art pug cliche normcore. Chia asymmetrical gochujang truffaut, DIY chicharrones man bun blog. Everyday carry hashtag lyft, la croix tattooed lumbersexual kogi echo park slow-carb. Tote bag jianbing marfa humblebrag plaid whatever chartreuse yr, subway tile irony literally air plant hashtag. Pork belly echo park shoreditch typewriter live-edge, kombucha 90’s. Offal gastropub asymmetrical salvia kinfolk lumbersexual wolf. Subway tile seitan sustainable tilde banh mi tbh. Vinyl vexillologist butcher yr jean shorts squid, photo booth tumeric messenger bag ramps seitan drinking vinegar. Hella literally subway tile bushwick tacos. Messenger bag pork belly migas air plant. Quinoa pabst freegan, literally ugh skateboard tumeric. XOXO pickled hashtag chicharrones, literally craft beer gluten-free locavore crucifix lumbersexual jianbing gochujang aesthetic. Live-edge franzen raclette biodiesel skateboard williamsburg. Leggings freegan occupy selvage. Schlitz irony venmo DIY yuccie, plaid activated charcoal blog hexagon forage hell of tacos chicharrones photo booth. Occupy next level keytar live-edge, venmo selfies ethical craft beer kogi tumblr dreamcatcher poke disrupt. Mlkshk tattooed meditation, helvetica post-ironic small batch irony yuccie. Neutra cred farm-to-table readymade. Man bun truffaut salvia seitan, pug chartreuse DIY raw denim pinterest. Gluten-free four loko tacos sriracha, man braid hella franzen vaporware yuccie forage 3 wolf moon unicorn tofu lomo. Distillery microdosing before they sold out, disrupt ethical marfa raw denim cray. Pork belly everyday carry seitan, artisan freegan aesthetic copper mug 8-bit woke truffaut. Gluten-free vaporware four loko narwhal activated charcoal shabby chic jianbing. Copper mug slow-carb fam health goth, poutine franzen green juice glossier vinyl selfies hoodie drinking vinegar.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Part 4 - A New Post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/02/part-4-a-new-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 4 - A New Post" /><published>2019-02-02T23:57:47-08:00</published><updated>2019-02-02T23:57:47-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/02/part-4--a-new-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/02/part-4-a-new-post.html">&lt;p&gt;Uh, so, right, did it work?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Uh, so, right, did it work?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Do You Mean, Text Programmer?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/02/what-do-you-mean-text-programmer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Do You Mean, Text Programmer?" /><published>2019-02-02T13:15:55-08:00</published><updated>2019-02-02T13:15:55-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/02/what-do-you-mean-text-programmer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/02/02/what-do-you-mean-text-programmer.html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t think this is going to work because I moved my default collections directory.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I don’t think this is going to work because I moved my default collections directory.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">“All Hallows“</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/29/all-hallows.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="“All Hallows“" /><published>2018-10-29T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-10-29T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/29/all-hallows</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/29/all-hallows.html">&lt;p&gt;Integrating Ulysses with Jekyll workflow isn’t always smooth, but I think I can use External Folders pointed to my _posts folder to manage blog entries, like this one.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="build-log" /><category term="getting-started" /><summary type="html">Integrating Ulysses with Jekyll workflow isn’t always smooth, but I think I can use External Folders pointed to my _posts folder to manage blog entries, like this one.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jekyll is the doctor.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/17/layout-variables.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jekyll is the doctor." /><published>2018-10-17T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-10-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/17/layout-variables</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/17/layout-variables.html">&lt;p class=&quot;inline-slogan&quot;&gt;I moved the logic handling variations in resume section content out of the layout and into the content, where it belongs. My changes work in so far as the pages render as they did previously,  but Liquid is somehow not getting the page variable “verbosity”. It does display it, but it is not controlling the display of sections as I thought it should.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I moved the logic handling variations in resume section content out of the layout and into the content, where it belongs. My changes work in so far as the pages render as they did previously,  but Liquid is somehow not getting the page variable “verbosity”. It does display it, but it is not controlling the display of sections as I thought it should.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="build-log" /><category term="getting-started" /><summary type="html">I moved the logic handling variations in resume section content out of the layout and into the content, where it belongs. My changes work in so far as the pages render as they did previously, but Liquid is somehow not getting the page variable “verbosity”. It does display it, but it is not controlling the display of sections as I thought it should.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/08/build-log.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2018-10-08T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-10-08T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/08/build-log</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/08/build-log.html">&lt;p&gt;Keeping track of what I’m doing as I build my website in Jekyll/Liquid, hosted on GitHub for nuthin’, is a pleasure!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m liking it a lot so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve factored out a quick version, well, three quick versions of my resume without any fuss, and I can see how to further reduce the complexity of the markup and present the content more flexibly, BUT I thought I really must get the blog working first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, that took a while, huh?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="build-log" /><category term="getting-started" /><summary type="html">Keeping track of what I’m doing as I build my website in Jekyll/Liquid, hosted on GitHub for nuthin’, is a pleasure!</summary></entry></feed>